welcome back everyone
today we are going to play twist space, a GTNH add-on
this quick video will focus mostly on the (?) details of the (exact?) mod
and without further ado
our first highlight is an alternative version for a multi block steam forge hammer
but even before we look into it
the spotlight is quickly taken by the large steam alloy smelter
this expensive machine can do up to 48 parallels
requiring 1 amp of HV power to not void all of our (bronze?)
all that power is being generated by our new multi block solar boiler
which we'll see better later on
moving on we can use some expensive but efficient basic steam generators to power our EBFs
while this new generator can reach over unit energy efficiency
it doesn't turn itself off when the load is removed
and also can only produce LV power
so in MV we had to go back to steam turbines to overvolt our EBF
next after we centralized power and did one more EBF upgrade
we set up some automation to properly craft enough circuits for our next highlight
the eye of wood
this machine will produce many random resources in exchange of a lot of lava
however, due to how limited the options for sourcing lava are
even the machine itself is wondering if that trade is worth it
moving to an even more questionable machine
I shall present you the Mega Brick Blast Furnace
this machine will require you to fuel it coal to produce steel at whatever speed you can feed it
until it decides to live up to its name and breaking itself
back to actual progress
we moved on from using solar boilers
to some high efficiency natural gas generators
those will keep up our new small AE2 system
while we move on to the personal dimension
here we will meet two old friends we lost a long time ago
the processing factory and the processing array
and thanks to a twist space
we can also use dual input buses to ease automation
next we proceeded into building the usual infrastructure
which at this time will be powered by the lightning spire
unlike lightening rods
this bigger version doesn't require a thunderstorm to generate energy
it will however require a little bit of cryotheum to cool down
and some iron for the periodic repairs
next we made a mega distillation tower
where we on demand every sort of distillation from platline to oil processing
this was also made easier thanks to the advanced Mega Oil Cracker
which removes the strict requirements for input placements
then we built a maximum size advanced clean room
and if you thought this is big and white enough to make you go crazy
well you didn't think yet of the cost of those filters
unlike a normal clean room
this one has no maintenance and no energy cost
next to keep up with our everything main net on demand run
we built a mega chemical reactor
before we even finish our first fusion reactor
once we reach fusion
we built an advanced circuit assembly line
which has no input order requirement
and can hold multiple imprints
and if you thought this was overpowered
well the next machine is mind blowing
I shall present you the nether interface
just look at the output and the NEI crafting recipe
moving on we did a little bit of magic
just enough to get a laser meter miner
this multi block will quickly dig meters one row at a time with a bonus fortune of three
next to increase our magic automation speed
we build an industrial magic matrix
which can use over aura nodes and laser tier energy to speed up magic infusions
thanks to this machine
we can now make dozens of infusions per second
we also traded the risk of flux production with the risk of power fail
and if that machine was going to make you scream bloody hell
well keep that for our next machine
which is literally called bloody hell
as the name and all of that blood suggests
this machine will process blood magic altar recipes
and unlike the previous one
it doesn't even require energy to work
while I think those two are probably the best looking multi-blocks I ever seen in modded Minecraft
those are not the only good looking multi-block added by twist space
we also have stuff like the eco-sphere growth simulator
capable of making hundreds of thousands of logs per second
while using a single amp of UV energy
next to it we have the large industrial Cooking Factory
which can do coke oven recipes with maximum parallel
but that's not the only machine capable of doing integer 32 parallel
we also have a sifter
a mixer
a fluid heater
and a fluid extractor
that doubles as fluid solidifier （向下分句）capable of doing that
and if you thought Integer 32 parallel was too overpowered
well we also have machines capable of doing perfect overclock
like the electrolyzer
that also doubles as a centrifuge
finally, to conclude this series of overpower multi blocks
we also have a machine that does chemical reactor recipes for 1/10 of the energy cost
and on top of that
it also has some custom recipes that allow you to skip most of the chemical line processing steps
moving to some more complicated multi-block
we have this (valuable?) forge which uses pyrotheum to increase its heat capacity
while doing so, it also gains some energy discount
making neutronium super cheap
and of course to cool down all of those hot ingots
we also have a heat devourer machine
we also have a laser powered laser
that someday will achieve perfect overclock
and a 4 in 1 metal working machine
that at some point will accept laser energy
and of course 4 in 1 means we have to build four of those
we also have a wire mill that will grow its parallel count by becoming longer
and the last UV multi block we built is a giant vacuum furnace
and this one also will increase its parallel by becoming taller
next we made some micro-bacteria vats
those can make some quite big batches
which require some fine tweaking of the amount of fluid held in the output hatch to reach optimal efficiency
and with that, we can now afford the Mega Cutting Machine and the Mega Polarizer
in their smaller form
and yes those two can grow in size to achieve more parallelized speed
next after building a mega assembly line
which doesn't require input separation
and can do 128 parallel
we go back to our laser
which can make the cheapest DTPF fuel ever
by stacking the speed bonus from each of the casing upgrades
the other issue you normally have with DTPFs is the raw Infinity Catalyst
as usual, twist offers a new multi block to help with that
the general ore processing TST
which multiplies the output of pure raw ores by four
it also gives a crazy amount of gems from gem ores
and on top of that it can also do infinite parallels
keeping up with our new star core miner
capable of producing a crazy amount of minerals
to keep up with the new power requirement
we started working on an actual dyson sphere
to do so, we used the dyson launcher structure to send solar sails into space
and once we have some orbiting our star
we can start collecting that energy through our dyson (Earth cyber?) dish
and it was then that we realized that
this is not going to produce any meaningful amount of energy
we could improve our output by building our dyson sphere around a better star
but the output would only be 10 times more
which is still thousands of times less than what will be meaningful to us
at the same time, making enough solar sails with proper module management is probably expensive for the moment
so instead of turning those solar rays into energy
we started turning those into critical photons
which you can use to craft a bunch of machines
or for a better energy source, antimatter
after our failed attempt at a new way of gathering energy
we went back to our trusty naquadah fuel
and here we can easily merge all of the laser dynamo of our generator using laser smart nodes
next we use the super cheap battery recipes to clearly craft our gorge
which for the moment isn't much useful
since the mega volcano is about 1000 times more energy efficient
and the entropy destroyer has no problem cooling down an endless amount of hot ingots
the other usage of gorge won't be able to show off for a while is its plasma making capacity
this time we can quickly put an end to the growth of our fusion tunnel
with the tier 3 ball lightning
capable of making crazy amount of plasma for super cheap
and that combined with the other twist multi blocks
will make producing the DTPF fuel basically free
to put all of that stuff to good use
we needed a miracle on top of our assembly lines
the miracle top will perfectly overclock the crafting of any circuit or circuit part
overwhelming even a machine whose only purpose was to prevent power failing circuit conversion
anyways with this, we can now start our eye of harmony progression
which we can speed up thanks to three new machines
the first one is the Astral Computing Array
which will greatly speed up our search
thanks to its huge liquid cooler rack
next we have the twisted Large Disassembler
which can uncraft anything that was made in an assembler or assembly line
helping us recover some of the valuable materials contained inside our older eye of harmony casing
finally to power all of this
we started building a dyson sphere around a bigger star
endlessly shooting more and more mirrors around it
this dyson sphere setup has no upkeep costs
but by sending more mirrors
we can increase our energy production super linearly
however there is a limit at how much energy each our receiving station can collect
so we had to build a few more of those
this will give our eye of harmony progression a huge push
but it will still leave us with enough time to work on new multi-block
such as the matter manipulator Genesis
which can either produce concentrated UU matter
or huge amounts of normal UU matter
next we have the Miracle door
which will do alloy blast smelt recipes to ingot with infinite parallel
then we made a micro space time fabricator
which makes a couple of new parts and cheaper tesseracts
finally we have the super water purifier
which will make our water line redundant
and after a few more upgrades and some waiting time
we finally go to the point where we have some leftover astral arrays
which we can use to boost some machines
like the star core miner
or the dyson sphere ray receiving stations
and on that subject
we also figure out a better way of converting all of that sunlight into energy
we start by concentrating it all into critical photons
then after turning those into antimatter in the Miracle Top
we build a strange matter aggregator
where we can pack that antimatter into fuel rods
and this process surely does produce a huge amount of universium byproduct
and finally we burn the antimatter in an artificial star
doing so can yield an amount of power
that can go even higher than integer 64 energy units per tick
going back to our base
we built a prototype for a better DTPF
and the main gimmick this one has is that it can host some modules to boost its working properties
but even though we don't have the Perfect Singularity overclock module
we can't run it long enough to even consider reaching its 75 percent fuel discount
next we built the Nano Core
which with its perfect overclock
will save us from having to automate the Nano forge tier 4
but the real game changer was the indistinct tentacle
which can do any amount of assembly recipes in a fixed amount of time
and with this, we quickly crafted 100 astral arrays in a single crafting job
and even though making astral arrays was that easy
we realized we can use more unconventional ways
for starters, with the crazy amount of energy at our disposal
we can afford overclocking a 200 astral array eye of harmony
but since making universium like that is still too normal
we upgraded our matter aggregator
so that it will make a bit more universium as by product
and while both running and crafting that machine is relatively cheap
building and chunk loading it was the real hassle
and with that, we can finally start crafting our first stargate all in one craft
we then proceeded into liquefying it
and not worry about the time and energy requirements of such operations
all of our machines are perfectly overclocking
and are powered by the legendary wireless hatch
which will make anything craftable in one tick
and just like that we obtain the last item of this pack
the twist token
and I guess that was it
see you next time
bye bye
欢迎回来，各位
今天我们来玩 TST，一个 GTNH 的附属模组
这期短片会主要带大家看这个模组的一些细节内容
闲话少说
第一个亮点是多方块蒸汽锻造锤的替代方案
不过在看它之前
风头先被大型蒸汽合金炉抢走了
这台昂贵机器最多支持 48 并行
而且需要 1A HV 相当的蒸汽，不然就会吞掉我们的材料
这些蒸汽都来自新的多方块太阳能锅炉
后面会再细看
接着我们用一些昂贵但高效的基础蒸汽发电机给高炉供电
这发电机的效率甚至可以超过 1
但就算移除负载，它也不会自动停机
而且只能产出 LV 电压
所以到了 MV，我们还是得回到蒸汽涡轮来给高炉升压
接着我们把供电集中起来，又升级了一轮高炉
然后搭了些自动化来量产下个 TST 亮点所需的电路板
武德之眼
这台机器会消耗大量岩浆随机产出资源
但由于可用的岩浆来源很有限
连机器自己都像在质疑这买卖值不值
接下来是一台更“有争议”的机器
给大家介绍巨型砖高炉
这机器吃煤炼钢，基本你喂多快它就跑多快
直到它名副其实地把自己干爆
回到正经游戏主线
我们从太阳能锅炉毕业
换成高效率天然气发电机
用它给我们新的小型 AE 系统供电
随后我们搬进到私人维度
在这里，我们遇到了两个失散已久的老朋友
九合一工厂和大哥阵列
同时，多亏了 TST
我们还能用输入总成来简化自动化
接下来照常搭基础设施
主要由闪电尖塔供电
和避雷针不同
这个大号版本不需要雷暴也能发电
不过它需要少量极寒之凛冰来冷却
还要用一些铁做定期维护
然后我们做了巨型蒸馏塔
从铂处理到石化，各种蒸馏都能按需处理
这也得益于进阶巨型石油裂化机
它移除了输入仓摆放的严格限制
之后我们造了最大尺寸的 TST 超净间
如果你觉得它又大又白得让你发狂
那你还没算过这些过滤器的成本
和普通的超净间不同
这个没有维护和能耗成本
接着为了跟上我们主网的各种按需生产
我们先把巨型化学反应釜建了
甚至在第一台聚变反应堆完工前就做出来了
进入聚变阶段后
我们做了进阶电路装配线
它没有输入顺序要求
还能同时放多个压印电路
如果你觉得这已经超模
那下一台更离谱
请看地狱接口
看一眼它的产出和 NEI 配方就懂了
接着我们稍微补了点魔法线
够做出激光陨星采矿场就行
这个多方块会一行一行高速挖陨星，还自带时运 III
为了进一步加速魔法自动化
我们造了工业注魔矩阵
它能用充能节点和激光仓来加速注魔
多亏这台机器
我们现在每秒能跑几十次注魔
也把“污染风险”换成了“断电风险”
如果刚才那台已经让你喊离谱
那把这句话留给下一台机器
因为它名字就叫血狱祭坛（bloody hell）
从名字和血量你就知道
这机器专门跑血魔法祭坛配方
而且和前一台不同
它甚至不需要电就能工作
这两台可能是我在所有 MC 模组里见过最好看的多方块
但 TST 里的好看多方块不止它们
还有拟似生态圈
每秒能产几十万原木
同时只吃 1A UV 电力
旁边是大型工业炼焦厂
能以极限并行跑焦炉配方
但能做到 int32 并行的不止它
我们还有拾荒者（筛选机）
"小型"磁力搅拌机（搅拌机）
人类能源设施的核心装置（流体加热器）
以及物质形态转换器（流体提取机）
它还能兼任流体固化机（向下分句）都能达到 int32 并行
如果你觉得 int32 并行已经太强
那我们还有能完美超频的机器
比如分子解构器（电解机）
它还兼任离心机
最后给这堆超模的多方块收个尾
还有一台机器能用 1/10 能耗跑化学反应配方
而且最关键的是
它有一堆自定义配方，能跳过大多数化工产线
再看一些更复杂的多方块
我们有这台锻炉，它用烈焰之炽焱提升热容
同时还能获得能耗折扣
让中子生产便宜得离谱
当然，为了冷却这些热锭
我们还做了热能饕餮
还有一台用激光仓的激光蚀刻机
未来某天也能达到完美超频
以及一台四合一金属加工机
后期会支持激光供能
当然，四合一的意味着我们得造四台
还有一台线材轧机，它会通过变长来提高并行数
我们最后做的 UV 多方块是巨型真空干燥炉
它同样会通过变高来提升并行
接着我们做了几个细菌培养缸
这东西能跑非常大的批次
但要达到最佳效率，需要精调输出仓里的流体量
有了这些，我们终于能做巨型切割机和巨型磁化仪了
先做小尺寸版本
没错，这两台都能扩容来换更高并行与速度
然后我们做了巨型装配线
它不需要输入隔离
并且能跑 128 并行
接着回到我们的激光机
它能做出有史以来最便宜的 DTPF 燃料
靠的是叠加每级外壳升级的速度加成
而 DTPF 的另一个常见瓶颈是无尽催化剂
照例，TST 又给了对应多方块来解这个问题
通用矿物处理厂 TST
它能把原矿产量乘 4
宝石矿也会给出夸张数量的宝石
而且还能跑无限并行
足以跟上新的星核钻机
后者的矿物产量同样离谱
为了跟上新的电力需求
我们开始做真正的戴森球
我们用戴森球模块发射场把太阳帆持续打入太空
当恒星周围有了足够太阳帆
就能通过戴森球射线接收站开始收集能量
然后我们发现
这点发电量几乎没有意义
虽然可以换更好的恒星提高产出
也就提升约 10 倍
离我们需要的级别还是差了几千倍
同时，做足够的太阳帆并处理模块管理，现在成本也很高
所以与其把这些太阳射线用来直接发电
我们改成先做临界光子
它可以拿去做很多机器
或者进一步做更强的能源：反物质
在新发电方案失败后
我们又回到了靠谱的硅岩发电
这里我们用激光智能节点，把发电机的所有激光源仓并到一起
接下来我们用超便宜的电池配方做出神缎
但它当前用处不大
因为熯焱高炉的能效高了约一千倍
而热能饕餮也能轻松处理近乎无限数量热锭的冷却需求
神锻另一个暂时用不上的能力是等离子生产
这次我们能快速结束聚变隧道的扩建
靠的是三阶球状闪电
它能以超低成本产出海量等离子体
再配合其他 TST 多方块
DTPF 燃料基本就等于白送
为了把这些都用起来
我们需要在装配线的顶点“创造奇迹”
奇迹顶点能对任何电路板和电路板部件实现完美超频
强到连专门防止电路板转换供不上能的机器都被它压过去
总之有了它，我们就能开始发展鸿蒙之眼
而且可以用三台新机器提速
第一台是星规阵列
它会显著加快研究速度
核心是超大的液冷机架
第二台是 TST 大型拆解机
它能拆解任何装配机或装配线做出来的物品
帮我们回收旧鸿蒙之眼外壳中的珍贵材料
最后，为了给这整套供能
我们开始围着更大的恒星造戴森球
不断向轨道发射更多太阳帆
这套戴森配置几乎无维护成本
而通过发射更多太阳帆
产能可以超线性增长
但每个接收站都有接受能量上限
所以我们又补了几口锅
这会狠狠推进鸿蒙之眼的进度
但我们仍有空档去做新多方块
比如质量发生器：创世纪
它可以产浓缩 UU 物质
也可以产海量普通 UU 物质
接下来是奇迹之门
它能以无限并行跑锭的合金高炉配方
然后我们做了微型时空发生器
它能做一些新部件和更便宜的超立方体
最后还有完美水体制造器
直接让净化水线变得多余
经过几轮升级和等待后
我们终于有了多余的星阵
可以拿去强化一些机器
比如星核钻机
或戴森球射线接收站
关于戴森球的话题
我们也找到了更好的“阳光转能源”方案
先把阳光全浓缩成临界光子
再在奇迹顶点里转成反物质
然后上奇异物质聚合器
把反物质封进燃料棒
这套流程会产出大量宇宙素副产物
最后把反物质塞进人工恒星燃烧
这会释放极其恐怖的电力
输出甚至能超过 Int64 EU/t
回到基地后
我们做了新版 DTPF 原型机
它的核心机制是可插模块来强化工作属性
但即便我们没有奇点无损超频控制器模块
它也跑不了多久，更别提吃到 75% 燃料折扣
接下来我们建了展开的纳米核心
凭借完美超频
它让我们不用再自动化四阶纳米缎炉了
但真正的外挂是不可视之触
它能在固定时长内完成任意数量装配配方
靠它我们一次下单就做出了 100 个星阵
但即使星阵已经这么好做
我们还能另辟蹊径
首先，既然我们有海量电力
就能对 200 星阵的鸿蒙之眼直接超频
但要是这么做宇宙素还是太常规了
于是我们升级了奇异物质聚合器
让它能作为副产再多吐一点宇宙素
而且这机器造价和运行成本都不算高
真正麻烦的是建造占地和区块加载
有了这些，我们终于能一单做出第一座星门
然后把它液化
并且完全不用担心这套流程的时间和能耗
所有机器都是完美超频
并且由传奇无线能源仓供电
任何东西都能做到 1 tick 完工
就这样，我们拿到了整合包最后一件物品
Twist Token
我想这就算通关了
下次见
拜拜